# Matthew Bonneville

Gilbert, Arizona, United States



linkedin.com/in/matthew-bonneville-944a431a9



m.bonnev9@gmail.com

## Summary

I'm a loyal and hard-working individual with 6+ years of managing experience in two different industry. I've led diverse teams in both metric and production based environments. I have a passion for problem-solving and customer service. I'm currently attending a coding boot-camp offered thru U of A to expand my skill-set. Being a manager for so long makes me understand what it is to be a good employee.

### **Experience**



### **A** Student

University of Arizona Boot Camps

Jul 2020 - Present (2 months +)

Currently attending Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

# Team Lead

**GM Financial** 

Jul 2016 - Jul 2020 (4 years 1 month)

# Store Manager

Meridian Cleaners

May 2008 - Jan 2016 (7 years 9 months)

Full time manager in production/assembly/customer service for a small-scale dry-cleaning operation.

#### Education



### ■ University of Arizona

Web Development

2020 - 2020

Currently attending a coding boot-camp

### **Skills**

Problem Solving • Teamwork • Collaborative Problem Solving • Management • Kronos Timekeeping • Organization Skills • Decision-Making